I have new boxes from Amote which means I have new nylon outfits, nylon head suits to be precise
which I'm going to show you a lot of colors today
but if you know my videos you may have seen them already
I've shown the black one in an earlier Amote video
they have zipper in the back, they have gloves and socks attached
and they're super super stretchy, let me show it
because you can see it here very stretchy
and I've worn this before in a video I said so already I love to style them for example
with paradise pants and use them basically as a top I've also worn this one out already for a
birthday party I put some shorts on top of it because then you see them as tights and top
and I think they're great basic they're also really really comfortable so it's
definitely something you should check out and I do not only have black but
other colors and they do not only come in this variety with a closed crotch
area but also with an open crotch area all the products come in these cute
little boxes so perfect for gifting them too and they are wrapped in paper
okay it's confusing and I'm going to show you a blue one it's really easy to
put them on because they're so super stretchy it's just a bit tight for the
first time but they're getting a bit looser over time so it's basically like
you would wear tights. Almost the same fabric and stretch is not the important
part you have to watch out for but not to damage it with sharp objects like
your nails for example. And now for the arms.
Well, you just have to check where the thumb is.
Yeah.
Another tricky part is to grab the fabric with the glove already on, but it's totally
okay.
As you can see here, it's really long, so I'm super happy with it because it's super
comfortable.
distribute the fabric a bit. So it's one size. You can easily wear it if you're taller
than me or if you have more weight than me. So it's really stretchy.
Now I thought about something to put on top of it because I want to style it a
bit and I have this blue bodysuit. Let's see if it fits and of course I'm wearing
I'm wearing panties and a bra underneath because we're on YouTube.
I'm not getting tired to say that because in almost every video I'm wearing underwear
beneath something see-through.
People are commenting, you're not supposed to wear it with underwear but, you know, you
have to go to other pages for that kind of content and I'm not doing that.
That was super fast.
I kind of like this layering style I've done here with the blue bodysuit.
Because if you want to wear this somewhere outside and don't want to run around basically naked,
then it's cool to put something on top of these kind of catsuits, which I really like and have done often already.
So, yeah, I think it's a fun book. It's a fun color. Blue is, of course, the best.
now after blue comes what? Red of course and I have this red catsuit but I'm not going to
wear it today because I've already worn it check it out so I combined the red catsuit with the red
pants and this piece here which I cannot name anymore before YouTube turns this video 80 plus
but you know what I mean.
This nice accessory made of leather.
And what I love about this combination is with the open shoes
you can still see the catsuit because it functions as socks now.
And we have the seamless look here still at the top.
And I love this combination red and black and also with the gold.
I think that's a really stunning look.
I did not expect this to come out like that.
when I tried it on I initially only planned to wear it with the top part but I added all the other
parts as well and it is a lot but it's nice okay that was the red one and now I have this
nude color one this is obviously a nude one and it's basically one full body tights because
it's the same material, the same color, the same look and just up until your head and not only until here.
There is also a dress available in this material which doesn't look like much yet but again, super stretchy.
So I'm just going to pop it on top of this suit now.
It's basically a neck holder.
Let me figure out how to close it.
I'm now adjusting, I think there's a strap here which has to go high here.
Okay this is a live test and I can tell you that this does not really work because it
is super slippery, the dress on top of the catsuit, it's running up permanently, it's
not sticking here in the bust area. So I would not recommend to wear this on top of a catsuit
but it will stick better to your skin. So but you get the idea and I can show you the product
pictures. But what I will try now which should work definitely in a better way is I will put
another catsuit on top of this catsuit because then at least it can't escape to any other
place because it's going to be kept in place by socks and legs.
Just let me find it again.
This beautiful lilac one.
So as you can see I'm wearing them on top of each other which is fine.
I can feel it in my fingers and my toes that it's a bit more restricting because it's now
really tight.
But other places it's fine everywhere it's still very comfortable because it's super
stretchy.
I've worn this one before too for another video on which I put kind of like sexy spicy
lingerie cosplay outfits on top and I think it worked really really well together with
the pink in these outfits and yeah you can check out the whole video on my channel but
now I think we're done here for today I have a discount code for Amorti and also for Amorisi
which is their sister brand.
You can check that out in my description text underneath the video and also leave a comment,
a thumbs up and subscribe to my channel, all that kind of stuff.
I'm happy if you support me.
So thank you for tuning in again.
I hope you're having a nice day.
See ya, bye!